

Profile

Hi there im full-stack developer with 5 years of experience and continuing. If your looking for a developer who can work, adapt quickly, and be experienced enough to match your expectations and open to sharing better ideas then hire me!

Employment History

Fullstack, Positive Nation

NOVEMBER 2023 - PRESENT

Fullstack maintenance and development and converting Figma/illustrator to responsive web design.

- Php (Laravel, PDO, WordPress, Vue js, Stripe, Node JS)
- SQL (MariaDB, Mysql Workbench)
- Bootstrap 5 (Jquery & vanilla js)
- GIT (Bash, Github Desktop, BitBucket)
- Webhosting (Justhost, A2hosting)
- Putty

Freelancer Web Developer

APRIL 2017 - PRESENT

Freelance web developer maintenance, development and web design.

- Php (Core, Laravel, Codelgniter, WordPress, Shopify, Node JS)
- SQL (MariaDB, MYSQL Mysql Workbench)
- Bootstrap 5 (Jquery & vanilla js)
- Tailwind (Tailwind UI, Flowbite, Vite JS & vanilla js)
- GIT (Bash, Github Desktop)
- Webhosting (Heroku, A2hosting, GoDaddy, Hostinger)
- Excel (VBA)
- Putty

Software Developer, Avalade

OCTOBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2023

Web App development (SLDC Waterfall) with APIs and performing research analysis and testing for web technologies, converting Figma/illustrator to responsive web design.

- Php (PDO, Matomo(Piwik), Zend, WordPress plugin, CMS, Smarty Template, Angular 12, Node JS)
- WebAR (AR js)
- SQL (MariaDB, Mysql Workbench)
- Bootstrap 5 (Jquery & vanilla js)
- Tailwind (Tailwind UI, Flowbite, Vite JS & vanilla js)
- GIT (Bash, Github Desktop, BitBucket)
- AWS (RDBMS, RESTful API)
- Figma

Software Developer, Axpara

OCTOBER 2021 - NOVEMBER 2023

Details

Bayambang Philippines 09217635295

jimenez.carlo.llabor@gmail.com

Skills

PHP (Core, Laravel, Codelgniter, Wordpress)

JS (Vue Js, Jquery)

CSS (Bootstrap, Tailwind)

SQL (Mysql, Mssql)

Git

Webhost (A2hosting, justhost, goDaddy, Hostinger)

Languages

English

Tagalog

Web App development (SLDC Waterfall) with APIs and performing research analysis and testing for web technologies, converting Figma/illustrator to responsive web design.

- Php (PDO, Matomo(Piwik), Zend, WordPress plugin, CMS, Smarty Template, Angular 12, Node JS)
- WebAR (AR js)
- SQL (MariaDB, Mysql Workbench)
- Bootstrap 5 (Jquery & vanilla js)
- Tailwind (Tailwind UI, Flowbite, Vite JS & vanilla js)
- GIT (Bash, Github Desktop, BitBucket)
- AWS (RDBMS, RESTful API)
- Figma

Systems Analyst Programmer, Concerted management Corporation(CMC), Quezon City

2021 - OCTOBER 2021

 $\label{thm:control} Technical Support, Web \, App\, maintenance\, and\, development\, (Scrum)\, with\, centralized\, flow.$

- Php (Codelgniter, Laravel)
- SQL (MYSQL, Mysql Workbench)
- Bootstrap (3-5) (Jquery & vanilla js)
- GIT (Bash, Github Desktop, Gitlab)
- Putty

Systems Analyst Programmer, H2Software, Pasig City

OCTOBER 2019 - JUNE 2021

Technical Support, Web App developement (Scrum) with centralized flow.

- Php (Codelgniter, Laravel)
- SQL (MYSQL, Mysql Workbench)
- Bootstrap (3-5) (Jquery & vanilla js)
- GIT (Bash, Github Desktop, Gitlab)
- Putty

Software Developer, I-Remit, Pasig City

FEBRUARY 2019 - JUNE 2019

On-the-phone & Software Support, Software maintenance, Development and web service API's (in XML).

- Php Core (ODBC)
- ASP.NET C# Razor(MVC, EF)
- SQL (MSSQL)
- Bootstrap4 (Jquery & vanilla js)
- GIT (Github Desktop)

Education

Bachelore, University of Pangasinan Phinma, Dagupan

FEBRUARY 2012 - MARCH 2018

Internships

Programmer, DILG, Baguio

JANUARY 2018 - MARCH 2018

On-the-phone support, troubleshooting, excel encoding, and wrote scripts in Excel (via vba) to automate work load.

References

Josel pambid from SPI Global(Technical lead)

pambid.josel@gmail.com | 09157181356

Jayr Desiderio Dumalag from I-Remit (Senior Software Developer)

desideriodumalag@gmail.com | 09088135561

John Russel B Dellosa from CMC (Fullstack Developer)

johnrusseldellosa25@gmail.c | +639381658616